COMPUTER NETWORKING AND TECHNICAL SUPPORT GRADUATE



- mikhaelhamoy@gmail.com
- 98 Fisherville Rd.
 Toronto, ON M2R 3C2
- Linkedin.com/in/mikhaelhamoy917

ABOUT ME

Graduate of Computer
Networking and Technical
Support with at least five
years of customer service
experience.

Advance IT knowledge with the ability to work in a fast-paced environment. Fast learner, problem solver, multitasker, enjoy challenges, strong attention to detail, excellent oral and written communication, punctual and deadline-oriented, coachable and resourceful in finding solutions, can work autonomously and with a team, proactive, and data-driven.

T E C H N I C A L S K I L L S

Hardware

Assembly, Maintenance, Peripherals, Printers, Drivers, Troubleshooting

Servers

Windows Server 2008 and 2012, CentOS7

Virtualizations

VMWare Workstation, Oracle VM VirtualBox, Windows Hyper-V

Databases

MySQL, Oracle SQL Developer

Networks

Configuration, Servers, Routers, LAN Technology

Security

Virus Protection, Maintenance, Monitoring, Backup Management, Disaster Recovery

Scripting

UNIX Shell, PowerShell, Python

EDUCATION

Computer Networking and Technical Support

Seneca College | Toronto ON | 2016 – 2019

Major Project: Create, monitor, and maintain a small autonomous system with a Linux Server, a Windows Server, a Router, and a Client.

Course Highlights: Windows and Linux Server Administration, Data Communications,
Database Management System, Information System Security,
Networking, Shell Scripting, Business Report Writing

EXPERIENCE

Fulfillment Center Associate I

Amazon | Mississauga ON | 2021 — Present Stow inbound products.

Crew Trainer

McDonald's Canada | Toronto ON | 2016 - 2021

Expert all-around team member.

- Train new production team members.
- Ensure that all team members are following McDonald's standards to provide topmost customer service.

Merchandiser

SPAR Canada | Vaughan ON | 2016 - 2021 Support merchandiser.